# Harry Zhu

San Francisco, CA | harryzhu45@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/harryjzhu | github.com/HarryZ10 | harryzhu.com

#### Summary

First-generation college graduate with proven leadership experience mentoring 45+ students and managing 50+ campus organizations. Technical background from F5 and Recidiviz internships combined with event planning expertise. Passionate about supporting first-gen and POC students through mentorship and community building.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Director of Student Associations & Clubs — George Fox University

August 2023 – April 2024

- Coordinated onboarding for 80+ club leaders, conducting 20+ leadership development group sessions
- Automated club expenditure system using Google Apps Script, reducing approval timeline by 93% while managing 100+ form submissions and a \$50K operating budget
- Led two biannual club president roundtables to guide cross-club collaboration, leading to 20+ joint campus events

#### **Treasurer** — George Fox Asian Student Union

August 2023 - April 2024

- Managed a \$4K annual budget for cultural events and club activities, implementing digital tracking systems to improve expense transparency by 40%
- Organized AAPI cultural week through panels and exhibits that attracted 100+ attendees and engaged 10+ alumni

## Lab Fellow (Part-Time) — George Fox College of Engineering

August 2022 – April 2024

- Developed personalized mentoring approaches for 40+ diverse learning styles, resulting in 70% of tutored students showing improved academic performance
- Created inclusive study environments for 45+ students from various technical backgrounds, adapting communication styles to bridge knowledge gaps and build student confidence

## **President** — George Fox ACM Chapter

August 2022 – May 2023

- Led a team of 4 officers to organize 12+ technical workshops and speaker events, increasing member engagement by 40% for annual hackathon event of 20+ participants
- Delivered 5+ weekly production builds for ACM-related websites using React and Node/Express, streamlining club marketing and reducing administrative workload by 90%
- Managed a total of \$2K operating budget and achieved 90% increase in alumni engagement rate (22% cumulative) for an annual hackathon through strategic partnerships with locally-grown, Oregon-based company, Silverpine

## Professional Experience

## Software Engineer Intern (Full-Time) — F5 Networks

July 2024 – September 2024

- Implemented automated debugging using **Bash** shell scripting in Kubernetes-driven containers to analyze **100**+ CI/CD pipelines resulting in **70**% faster crash analysis for **45**+ **developers** on F5's core traffic management system
- Iteratively refined crash analysis procedures through feedback from 3 departments, incorporating suggestions from 30+ engineers to create a solution that gained team-wide adoption
- Expanded knowledge sharing by creating documentation on crash analysis procedures, supporting 30+ developers

# **Software Engineer Intern** — George Fox Communications Office

August 2021 – April 2024

- Streamlined content review time by 95% of 4,000+ pages through an API-driven content management system monitoring web portal using VueJS, Docker, PostgreSQL, NodeJS and migration tools
- Enhanced user experience for 1,000+ daily visitors through performance and design optimization of 100+ pages

#### Software Engineer Intern (Full-Time) — Liminal Insights, Inc.

June 2023 – August 2023

- Reduced configuration time by 90% by developing NextJS and Python containerized services using Docker
- Enabled industrial-scale battery testing reliability by architecting a high-throughput, message-oriented system that processes 50+ debug logs per minute while maintaining testing throughput through ZeroMQ-based process isolation

- Eliminated 200+ OWASP security vulnerabilities (including XSS, CSRF, and package dependency issues) through automated scanning and remediation, strengthening platform security by 98% for state-level criminal justice data
- Built API-driven security account automation system handling 15+ annual departures using Docker and Python frameworks, driving 95% efficiency gain in audit workflows until replacement by enterprise SOC2 solution in 2024
- Prevented potential security incidents through implementation of 10 new security controls in Google Cloud

## **EDUCATION**

## George Fox University

Graduated April 2024 Newberg, OR

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (GPA: 3.55)

Awards: Computer Science Department Annual Scholarship, Stevens Endowed Scholarship (2022), Pablo M. Ortiz Computer Science Scholarship (2023), 2x Top 500 National Cyber League Competitor (2023-2024)

Leadership Activities: Tech Lead (2022-23) & President (2023-24) for Association for Computing Machinery Student Chapter, Director of Student Organizations (2023-2024), Yearbook Co-Director (2020-2024), Treasurer for Asian Student Union (2023-2024)